Snakes and Ladders the ultimate game of
chance no strategy no skill just a roll
of the die there is no way to get good
at this game but here I am obliterating
my family game after game one again for
me would be
good that's insane with near perfect
luck coupled with their unmitigated bad
luck you know real six here oh Absolut
no yeah let's go
sex one 2 3 what you do that this is how
I became the world's greatest Snakes and
Ladders
[Music]
player Snakes and Ladders is the perfect
game to teach children all about the
unjust nature of life you might get a
ladder that allows you to skip a few
steps and then bam the 2008 credit
crunch happens and all your job
prospects are shattered you work your
way through a career that you hate
diligently and then bam mortgage rates
triple looks like another 5 years of
renting for you
pleb a that's a bummer it's important to
teach these kids the brutality of this
economy before the ages of five to
toughen them
up so how can you gain an edge in a game
seemingly based purely on chance well
the weakness has to be in the die how
can you make sure your opponent gets bad
rules that send them down the snakes
whilst also ensuring you get favorable
rules up the
ladders let's see if we can make that
[Music]
happen
oh
[Music]
all right here is the dice I give it a
quick coat off lacquer just to make it
all gorgeous and it came out like
really really well and obviously it's
magnetic so these little coin magnets
move it around and I can change its
polarity all right we have a loaded die
with embedded magnets so if you hold
another magnet under the table you can
roll a one or a six every time depending
on which end of the magnet you use
however it's actually impossible to win
the game that way since you would need
to land on 100 exactly and obviously
your opponent will just roll the same
numbers as you we need to control what
we get and for that we need the magic of
[Music]
electronics
here's how all this works the four
electromagnets controlled by a switch
and the ardino can change their polarity
when these are glued under the table I
can make the die roll a one or a six on
command see from the top of the desk
underneath the
desk secrets are revealed here are four
electromagnets using these two numbers I
can achieve a near perfect game in just
seven Rolls of the die likewise I can
sabotage my opponent by stalling them
with constant ones or sending them down
snakes when a six or a one roll would be
bad for them so if you roll it just
right you can roll a six every
[Music]
time how about a
one oh did you see
that sometimes it's a little bit
suspicious so there's another
one that was
suspicious the magnets are even strong
enough to change the result post roll
which is a little unnerving if you want
to be really sneaky you can actually
just turn it off and if someone rolls
like a three or something you can kind
of coax it into being a six or you can
flip the switch and it becomes a
one pretty weird
right before observing how people react
to being crushed at snakes and ladders a
quick word from this week's sponsor
thorum thorum specializes in extremely
unique rings made from unconventional
materials I went for the Hercules ring
made from tongen and lignum Vite the
hardest wood paired with the hardest
metal I think the contrast between the
two materials just really pops thorum
makes a bunch of rings in unorthodox
Styles like this one made from a World
War II gun barrel it's nice to wear
something that's just a little bit more
interesting than a standard plain band
that men usually wear these can make
perfect wedding rings and they do come
in ladies versions and sets all rings
come with a lifetime warranty and incl
include free shipping even
internationally I also got myself the
meteorite watch which has an extremely
sleek and clean design with a tiny slice
of real gibian meteorite embedded in the
face it's cool to own something so
modern looking that also contains a 4
and A2 billion year old piece of
meteorite the watch is also mechanical
so no battery changes ever my viewers
can get 20% off a truly unique piece
with the code Mike B so if you're
planning on tying the kn or just want a
unique ring that contains an actual
dinosaur bone check out thorum and
thanks to thorum for sponsoring this
week's
video right then time to test it on some
unsuspecting victims if I lose I will
clean out the cats litter for one year
but that's your job anyway I know but I
don't do it very much I want to choose
what I win all right what do you want I
get whenever I want a massage you have
to just do it for a year Your Role first
okay Snakes and Ladders six what color
am I 1 two three four five six well done
I could do with a one yay
one straight up to 21 oh I forgot that
you can go up to the
laders
yeah right six initially nothing seemed
ay right six up to 69 okay uh a one for
you would be bad a one oh that was one
unfortunate for you it just seemed like
a rotten bit of
[Music]
luck one ah unfortunate for you God this
is really confusing all the way back
down that's such a confusing game I just
need a six to win the game uh so let's
just hope that happens ah perfect so I
have to bring you a cup of tea every
day however my poor acting eventually
gave rise to suspicion right you want to
rematch best of three yeah one again for
me would be
good perfect that's
[Music]
insane right I need a SE to win the game
cuz that'll take me to
100 ah
perfect right one now wait what do you
win M if you win I win my mother's
approval me a
sex
yes yeah let's go
SE one two three what you do that look I
guess you don't want to one that's
shaed I look
at a six would be bad for
you oh it's actually a
six one 2 three four five
six that's a bummer H it's a bummer for
you I'm sorry can really use a
six 1 2 3 4 5 what would be good for you
all you want right oh so the table moves
yeah I want I one again one
yeah it was six it was
one you only real six here oh absolute
[Music]
NE I about
St what is going
[Music]
on I did the one hey it was a six it was
it was a six that's a bummer right a six
for me however would be the end of the
game two a two a two one one one a two
a that's a bomber right I want give me a
1 2 3 4 do not give me a
[Music]
six so there we have it a loaded die
designed to destroy everyone at snakes
and ladders I hope you enjoyed this
style of video if you'd like more of
this type let me know in the comments
and if you haven't already subscribe it
really helps out the channel see you
next time
peace
a